<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Noida International University</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Home</string>
    <string name="title_section2">About NIU</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Schools</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Academics &amp; Fee</string>
    <string name="title_section5">Admission @ NIU</string>
    <string name="title_section6">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="title_section7">Study Material</string>
    <string name="title_section8">Latest Announcements</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="list_title">Downloadable Files</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="about_devs">About Developers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_description">This Application is not officially launched by Noida International University. \n This application is maintained by students of Noida International University pursuing in B.Tech 4th Year. Students, who are interested in developing android Apps can support us for further development of the Application.</string>
    <string name="email">sandeep.rana011@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="dev_name">Sandeep Rana,\nSonu Raghav \n \t \&amp; \n Manish Saraswat</string>
    <string name="mobile">+91\-8439740563</string>
    <string name="mobile2">+91\-9891255422</string>
    <string name="sirfirey_devs">Sirfirey Devs</string>
    <string name="facebook_link">http://www.facebook.com/sandeep.rana011</string>
    <string name="help_app">This application is especially developed for the students of Noida International University. By using this application students can download their specific class Notes and useful Files in just a \"Single Click\". </string>
    <string name="app_use">Application Uses</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="address_niu">Noida International University Campus:\nPlot 1, Sector-17 A, \nYamuna Expressway,\nGautam Budh Nagar, UP, \nINDIA (203201)</string>
    <string name="icon_desc">Buttons Descriotion</string>
    <string name="icon_des_help">-Opens Help.</string>
    <string name="icon_des_exit">-Exits application.</string>
    <string name="icon_des_about_us">-Opens About Us screen.</string>
    <string name="icon_des_share">-Opens share application window.</string>
    <string name="icon_des_refresh">-Refresh content List.</string>
    <string name="icon_des_find">-Content Finder</string>
    <string name="icon_des_home">-Home Button.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_text_file_view">Text File</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_screen">Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_load_text">Activity_loadText</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_niu">AboutNIU</string>
    <string name="why_niu">\tWhy Noida International University? The answer is why not? When celebrated names in the teaching faculty, professors, eminent scholars, scientist and renowned academicians from all over the world are part of the academic council, academic team and faculty members should there be any other reason to choose some other educational institutions?
\n\n\tNIU offers international as well as domestic students one of the most inviting places to pursue their careers. Offering possibly the widest range of graduate and undergraduate courses to choose from, NIU also enhances the learning experiences with access to a state of the art electronic library, IT infrastructure, easy educational loans and scholarship and a very friendly and supportive educational staff.\n\n\tAlso apart from offering the best in educational services, NIU also assists students by offering them a wide range of accommodation to choose from.\n\n\tAnd then there is always the world class sports facilities and the coolest cafeteria to hang out and decide whether any other universities would match up to such standards\n</string>
    <string name="vc_message">\tAs Vice Chancellor of Noida International University I am delighted to extend a very warm welcome to you. Choosing a university is one of the most important decisions you will make in your life and will be influenced by many factors such as the reputation of the University, its location, and facilities.
\n\n\t
Noida International University is situated within the city of Gautam Budh Nagar, which is a vibrant multicultural city that has scripted its own success story. The city offers a large choice of cultural activities.
\n\n\t
Education is about much more than employability. It includes evolving with a different view, developing different perspectives and opening your mind to the possibilities and emerging as world class championship material. The balance of theory and practice at the University, incorporating the key relationships we hold with local, national and international partners, will prepare you for chosen careers.
\n\n\t
Noida International University will give you the ability, self-confidence and the desire to go on learning for the rest of your life and to cope with new situations. Studying at Noida International University will give you the skills and knowledge to open up the opportunities that come from having a receptive and enquiring mind.
\n\n\t
Noida International University provides an orientation programme to help you settle into your new home and our dedicated team at the Admissions Office and Student Services will do all they can assist you.
\n\n\t
I wish you every success and we look forward to welcoming you to Noida International University in the near future.</string>
    <string name="our_foundation">\t
The hallmark of Noida International University (NIU) is its celebrated academic team, academic council and faculty members. In fact, NIU is the centre where finest minds from the most revered institutions of the country and abroad congregate to share their expertise and pursue knowledge.
\n\n\t
NIU celebrates the diversity of knowledge among its scholars and their expertise in their fields to interdisciplinary challenges that cross traditional academic boundaries. The NIU faculty harmoniously blends scholarly research with dynamic classroom teaching.</string>
    <string name="grow_up">\t
An internationally acclaimed teaching fraternity, competitive courses, international students, a world class campus and the joy of discovering one of the richest and most enchanting cultures of the world, welcome to Noida International University (NIU).
\n\n\t
Located in one of the most promising economic districts of the country and situated in NCR Delhi, the Noida International University (NIU) offers infinite opportunities for self motivated individuals for their intellectual, personal and professional development.
\n\n\t
As the focus is on learning, NIU offers students international facilities for a rich and interactive personalised learning expereince, a one-on-one interaction with some of the most respected and highly acclaimed masters in their respective fields of specialisation. We also offer a diverse range of extra-curricular activities and top-rated career services that further boost student employability.
\n\n\t
Apart from the very best of international courses, NIU will also introduce students to an attractive living environment that is home to a multicultural community. An international village of sorts. NIU lets them choose from a host of attractive living environments to enrich their social life while balancing responsibilities and pursuing goals.</string>
    <string name="hostel_fee">1. AB HOSTEL-BOYS
\n
\tI. 3 seater (cooler)-60000 per \n\tannum+5000(security)refundable
\tII. 3 seater (AC)-75000 per \n\tannum+5000(security)refundable
\n
2. AS HOSTEL-BOYS
\n
\tI. Double Seater-Cooler-70000+5000(Security Refundable)
\tII. Double Seater-AC-85000+5000(Security Refundable)
\tIII. Three Seater – Cooler- 60000+5000(Security Refundable)
\n
1. LAUREATE -GIRLS
\n
\t\tI. 3 seater (AC)-75000 per annum+5000(security)refundable
\n
2. Khushboo Apartments-GIRLS
\n
\tI. Double Seater-Cooler-60000+5000(Security Refundable)
\tII. Single Seater-Cooler-70000+5000(Security Refundable)
\tIII. Double Seater-AC-75000+5000(Security Refundable)
\tIV. Single Seater-AC-85000+5000(Security Refundable)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="title_activity_webview">WebviewActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_news_feeds">NewsFeeds</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_map">MapActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_class_list">ClassList</string>
    <string name="manish">Manish Saraswat\nmanishsuperstar9@gmail.com\n+91-9810483143</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tea_pro_activity">Teacher\'s Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notes">Notes</string>
    <string name="link_result">http://sandeeprana011.hostfree.us/result/result.php?table_name=NIU_SET&amp;enroll_no=11SETBTCS3095&amp;sem=7&amp;prf=5187</string>
    <string name="title_activity_result">Result</string>
    <string name="notes_heading">Faculty Dashboard</string>
    <string name="results">Results</string>
    <string name="updates">Updates</string>

    <string-array name="table_name">
        <item>School of Architecture</item>
        <item>School of Education</item>
        <item>School of Eng. &amp; Tech</item>
        <item>School of Sciences</item>
        <item>School of Law</item>
        <item>School of Jour. &amp; Mass Com.</item>
        <item>School of Nursing</item>
        <item>School of Fine Arts</item>
        <item>School of Liberal Arts</item>
        <item>School of Defence, Security &amp; Intelligence</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_admit_card">AdmitCard</string>
    <string name="sof_science">Introduction:  The School of Sciences in Noida International University started with the challenge of imparting good quality theoretical and practical education in the different disciplines of science. The School of Sciences offers Bachelor’s Degree in Biotechnology, Microbiology, Physics, Chemistry and Mathematics and Master’s degree in Biotechnology, Microbiology, Bioinformatics, Statistics, Physics, Chemistry and Mathematics.  At present, along with these programs, the School of Sciences also offers Doctoral programs in Biotechnology, Microbiology, Biochemistry and Chemistry.  The functions of the School are to:      Plan, develop and offer academic programs at, Undergraduate, Post-Graduate and Doctoral levels.     Encourage research in discipline-based as well as systemic areas.     Collaborate in the development of programs/courses offered by other schools of the university.     Provide learner support using electronic media.     Participate in the development and monitoring of student support services.     Provide consultancy to organizations and training to each and every individual.     Organize and participate in workshops, conferences and seminars sponsored by national and international agencies with a view to improve transaction of science curriculum.  Department of Biotechnology:  The Department of Biotechnology has been started with the objective of giving new impetus to the development of the field of traditional as well as modern biotechnology. In just a year of its existence, the Department has promoted and accelerated the pace of development of biotechnology in the State. Through high class of teaching, demonstrations and creation of infrastructural facilities a palpable impact on the awareness about this field has been seen. The Department has made significant achievements in the growth and application of biotechnology in the broad areas of agriculture, plant sciences, animal sciences, environmental sciences, and industry. The Department is in process of signing MoUs with some DSIR recognized companies and organizations.  The Department runs following programs:      Ph.D. (Biotechnology)     Ph.D. (Biochemistry)     M.Sc. (Biotechnology)     B.Sc. (Biotechnology)  Department of Microbiology:  The Department of Microbiology aims at the study of microorganisms which plays an enormous role in our life. From the study of emerging infectious diseases to biotechnology, microbiology plays a vital role in basic and applied science. They constitute vast potential resources in varied areas such as food, feed, fuel, bio-fertilizer, pharmaceuticals, pigments, enzymes, besides combating pollution. There are abundant career opportunities in microbiology, an outstanding field for students interested to become professionals. The Department is focusing on applied aspects of microbes.  The Department runs following programs:      Ph.D. (Microbiology)     M.Sc. (Microbiology)     B.Sc. (Microbiology)  Department of Basic Sciences:  The Department of Basic Sciences is of vital significance in any academic and technical institution. The Department aims at providing world class academic knowledge in Mathematics, Physics, Statistics and Chemistry. The objective of these courses is to enable the students to acquire deep academic knowledge in basic sciences, attain proficiency and develop the skills to communicate efficiently to handle future jobs in academics and industry. The Department of Basic Sciences in the School of Sciences aims at making budding youngsters well-equipped and well versed in their prospective professional careers.  The Department runs following programs:      Ph.D. (Mathematics)     Ph.D. (Physics)     Ph.D. (Chemistry)     M.Sc. (Mathematics)     M.Sc. (Physics)     M.Sc. (Chemistry)     M.Sc. (Statistics)     B.Sc. (PCM)</string>
    <string name="sof_law"><![CDATA[The School of Legal Studies &amp; Research (SLSR) is committed to revolutionizing the learning experience through the introduction and creative use of pedagogical method which are regular feature at some of the world’s most-admired Universities. The faculty members at SLSR are highly qualified and experienced and have advance degrees in Law from renowned Universities.  Teaching Methodology  To enrich the learning experience of students, SLSR envisions teaching by combining case method with lecture method which is unique to SLSR in India. The special feature of teaching is the emphasis laid on understanding the latest developments in decisional law as well as legislations enacted by legislative bodies. Particular attention is paid to ensure student’s participation and interaction during the course of teaching by motivating them to read cases from the original law reports rather than from secondary sources such as text books.  The weekly seminar programme at SLSR seeks to provide a platform to discuss, analyse and debate contemporary national and international public issue, especially the legal dimensions thereof. The seminar series is designed to keep students and researchers at the SLSR abreast with recent legal developments. Regular participation and active interventions in discussions aim at enhancing the communication skills of the students, apart from improving their knowledge-base and self-confidence levels and polishing their personality traits qualities that are central to flourishing career in future. Other regular features of SLSR are moot court and quiz competitions.  Research Activities  SLSR proposes to start a quarterly law journal with the title “Noida International University Law Review” – the first issue of which is expected soon.  The Weekly Seminar Programme is a part of the regular academic activities at the SLSR. Regular participation and active interventions at the discussions aims at enhancing the communication skills of students, apart from improving their knowledge-base and self-confidence levels and polishing their personality traits. Some of the topics of the Weekly Seminar were the following:  The “Cash for Vote” Controversy, 20 September 2011  Path-Breaking Judgements of Mr. Justice Markandey Katju 30 September, 2011  Electronic Legal Research Demo by Westlaw India (29.09.2011)  “Corruption and Its Control by Lokpal and Lokayuktas”  “Federal Constitution with special reference to India”  “Fundamental Rights”  “Right to Life and Personal Liberty” (December 09, 2011)  Lecture by Eminent Legal Luminaries]]></string>
    <string name="sof_jms">In the last one decade, the field of media communications have undergone profound changes, more so because Marshal McLuhan’s prophesy of ‘global village’ has now been fully realized. The world is not big anymore because the media technologies have become bigger in abolishing and altering the sense of both time and space, globally. Media today is capable of influencing an individual’s life. Be it social, personal, political or cultural. Its power now encompasses the globe sweeping geographical boundaries, territorial distinctions and cultural limitations. The local is global today and real is virtual and vice versa. Developments in technology, politics and society have led to the role expansion of journalism and media with new set of social, cultural and political responsibilities. To make sense of such an increasingly intricate scenario communications schools today face enormous challenges in creating a pool of globally sound media professionals who are well attuned with the changing times. The School of Journalism and Mass Communication at Noida International University aims to create professionals who possess both intellectual and technical rigor of high calibre. The school is constantly working to innovate and improvise the knowledge delivery mechanism by introducing new-age pedagogy and teaching standards. Fresh pedagogical and methodological considerations have been employed by a dedicated team of young and veteran academics in designing the modules by reconciling key tenets of theory, practice, research and training to enhance one’s learning experience. The perfect combination of theory and practice determines our drive to produce talent which can go beyond the mechanical way of journalistic practice and produce work which is creative, informative, intriguing and entertaining in nature. To cater to the needs of the new age media industry, fresh technical modules such as digital filmmaking, cinematography, advanced digital photography, film production and non-linear editing have been complied and introduced at both bachelor and master levels. Specialised courses like 3D animation, cinema studies, event management and new-media advertising are soon to be added to SJMC’s growing academic profile. With a philosophy to emerge as knowledge producer in communications, constant efforts are underway at the school to initiate academic research of international standards focused on solving real-world issues. The faculties at the school are involved in regular development of their academic profiles, and regularly publish in both national and international journals. Our growing alliances with both industrial and international academic institutions inform and complement our urge for excellence.</string>
    <string name="sof_nursing"><![CDATA[The mission of the NIU – School of Nursing, is to improve the health of individuals and diverse communities locally and globally through leadership and excellence in nursing education, research, practice, and service. The academic rigor of the program is for shaping nursing graduates to be professionals. Our strength lies in the strategic creation of an environment that embodies excellence in research, teaching and practices and aim for growth that is planned, innovative, and financially sound.  The School of Nursing believes that “When you are a nurse you know that every day you will touch a life or a life will touch yours.”  We want to do what nobody else will do, a way that nobody else can do, in spite of all we go through; is to be a nurse. We want our nursing students to be the best in learning as well as in practicing. The vision of the School of Nursing is to nurture the most dedicated and service minded nurses to our nation as well as other parts of the world. The school believes that nursing is a form of art that requires devotion, preparation and highest level of commitment.  Career Opportunity:  Nursing has found its unique and indispensable place in hospitals, community health centres, medical clinics, nursing homes, armed forces, ships, aeroplanes and other spheres of human activity. Nursing has its many faces like hospital nurse, visiting nurses, doctor’s assistant in diagnosis treatment/research, health nurse, community health nursing, nursing practitioners and so on. A career in the exciting and interesting field of nursing, offers opportunities not only to be placed in countries around the globe of self advancements, self- achievement and job satisfaction.  The courses offered are: General Nursing &amp; Midwifery (3 and half years) and Auxiliary Nursing &amp; Midwifery (2 Years)  The Course Objectives:      Nurses on completion of this course will be able to:     Demonstrate competency in providing health care to individual, sick or well nursing care to individual, sick or well nursing process.     Assess the nursing needs of patients     Plan and carry out appropriate to nursing needs.     Provide effective nursing care for maintaining best possible level of health in all aspects.     Promote self-care in people under their care.     Apply problem solving techniques in nursing practices.     Evaluate effectiveness of nursing care.     Apply knowledge from the humanities, biological and behavioural sciences in functioning as a nurse.     Function effectively with members of the health team and community applying the knowledge of human relations and communication skills in her work.     Participate as member of the health team in delivery of curative, preventive, promotive and rehabilitative health care services.     Mobilise community resources and their involvement in working with the communities.     Demonstrate use of ethical values in their personal and professional life.     Demonstrate interest in activities of professional organisations.     Recognise the need for continuing education for professional development.     Demonstrate basic skills in teaching patients and giving nursing care to them.     Demonstrate basic skills in administration and leadership while working with other member of health team and community.     Assist in research activities.  Teaching methodology  The course offers both theory and practical sessions as per the INC ordinance. The classes will be handled by well-trained and experienced teachers. More emphasis will be given for self-development independent work through various teaching methods and utilizing the recent educational technology.]]></string>
    <string name="sof_finearts"><![CDATA[Art is has no barrier and understands no geography. It is a global activity which encompasses a host of disciplines, as evident from the range of words and phrases which have been invented to describe its various forms. Examples of such phraseology include: fine arts, liberal arts, visual arts, decorative arts, applied, arts, design, crafts, performing arts, and so on.  History is witness that great artists have showcased their talent with their brilliant art without the proper and formal basic education to make their identity in the world. Their brilliance and outstanding work in the area of art has gifted the world some of the rarest masterpieces ever seen till date. Today, in a country like India god gifted talent in arts are not recognized due to the tough rules and regulation of the education system. Their creativity and passion goes in vain rather than achieving greater heights.  Noida International University (School of Fine Arts) is on a unidirectional approach to cater these unrecognized budding artists, give them proper education in art and nurture their hidden talent and sharpen their skills for being a perfectionist in this competitive world. The School of Fine Arts provides wide range of techniques in the field of arts. Customized curriculum has been devised for the students to choose their choice of subjects as their specialization. Experienced faculties and industry based artists are also associated with the school to impart latest techniques of art so that students may face the commercial world. High class infrastructure is being developed to facilitate students for better understanding in an imaginative manner. In today’s world a scholar is judged by the marks in his degree but an artist is judged by his or her masterpiece.  Special features about the School of Fine Arts      Highly qualified &amp; experienced faculty     Extensive infrastructural support     Artistic and interactive environment     Collaboration with renowned artists     Regular workshops and presentations     Provision of theoretical notes     Educational &amp; academic tours     Industrial &amp; gallery visits     Kala mela “annual fest”     Spacious and facilitated class rooms     Foreign collaboration     Placement support]]></string>
    <string name="sof_liberalarts"><![CDATA[Our Vision  TheSchoolofLiberal Artscommenced with the establishment ofNoidaInternationalUniversity. The emphasis of the School of Liberal Arts (SLA) is to create a body of students who would be able to tackle the challenges and wrest opportunities in a rapidly changing world.  The focus of theSchoolofLiberal Artswill be on the students who will be empowered with the requisite knowledge and skill by exposing them to ideas and people from around the world. These exposures will help in developing in the individuals a very diversified, supportive and inclusive outlook so that they are empowered to tackle any situation that the future may bring.  Academic freedom and integrity and the continual support by the faculty will encourage the students to cultivate a culture wherein they would engage themselves in finding solutions to the pressing problems faced byIndiaat the global as well as in the domestic level. We believe that with better understanding and practice of liberal arts can makeIndiaa strong nation.  The School of Liberal Arts of Noida International University is characterized by these following aspects which demarcates it from other institutions.       Individual attention is paid to each student     A serene and competitive residential campus gives them the opportunity to live and learn from each other.     The proximity to the National Capital Region exposes them to a wide variety of cultural, political and intellectual exchanges among the students of different nationalities.     SchoolofLiberal Artsis training ground for the next generation of leaders and responsible citizens.     The curriculum of the School develops creative thinking and the ability of the students to see things as a complete whole.  Keeping the future of the students and the nation in mind we have therefore developed fully rounded responsible and innovative Post-Graduate, Under Graduate and Diploma Courses in Liberal Arts.  Our curriculum includes various aspects of study like, research, group discussion, seminars, workshops, visiting art galleries, theatres, museums and historical places etc. which would mould their thinking and will enhance their leadership skills and professionalism. Faculty Profile  Name: Kalpana Jayas  Qualification:  JRF –NET (History), M.A (History) from  Centre For advanced Studies in History , Aligarh Muslim Universty Aligrh , LL.B from Chaudhary Charan University,Meerut  Designation: Asst. Professor Email: kalpanajayas@gmail.com Teaching Experience:  7 Years Area of Teaching Interest: History &amp; Political Science Area of Research : India’s Asian trade during 17th century Research Publications: ‘English company’s participation in Indo-Persian trade during 17th century’ (published in 2002 in the volume of Indian history) Congress and the ‘Mughal documents on Achin’ (published in 2003 in the volume of Indian History Congress).    Name :Meenu Bathla  B.A (Hons) Eng., M.A (Eng.), M.Phil. (Eng.) Teaching Experience: 5 Years Area of interest: Professional Communication, English Literature, Personality Development, Soft skills, Business Communication Area of research: A study on pedagogy of Business English in India Research Publication:  “Teaching Business English as English for Specific purposes” presented in International Conference at University of petroleum &amp; energy Studies, Dehradun in November 2011. Students Experience in Campus:  This university has given me good opportunity to prove myself. I am getting chance to learn and explore to the best of my creative ability  Kaynat Khan, BA-IInd Sem  Noida International University is a very trusted and reputed university, our faculty is very good and cooperative. I am very glad to be the part of the University.  Shikha Tyagi, BA –IInd sem  Noida International University is very good university for higher education in my opinion. I am sure upon graduating from this University,I  shall have a bright future Shakeel BA-IInd sem – Afaghnistan]]></string>
    <string name="sof_architect">What a painter can do with a canvas and a handful of paint brushes, the architect can do with bricks and mortar. They are the ones who turn your of dreams into realities. Architecture is not just about building monumental masterpieces but it is also having the good sense to preserve Mother Nature in all her beauty. A good architect not only builds aesthetically pleasing monuments in keeping with the requirements of time but he also builds the nature along with these. The School of Architecture of NIU is one of the most sought after course. The school offers full time B. Arch courses in Architecture. The school draws its faculty from illustrious institutions of the country. NIU believes in recruiting reputed faculty who has been teaching this subject for long and has had practical experience in this field bring a new dynamism to the subject and to the department as a whole. Besides we also have visiting professors, professionals and well known architects who come to NIU to deliver their case studies and their experiences. At the NIU, School of Architecture, the core emphasis is not just in creating landmarks that withstand the test of time but it is also about possessing the knowledge for a greener earth. Keeping this in mind, the faculty at the school of architecture not only teaches the fundamental of the subject but they also teach the students on how to build a dream home without snatching anything from nature. The use of eco friendly materials, environmentally friendly methods of construction, recyclable materials and the maximum use of natural substances to beautify the construction is emphasized. Students are taken on field trips so that they can get a touch and feel of such materials and can use them when they finally start their career. Not only this they are also periodically tested to weigh their command over the subject vis a vis such green technologies.</string>
    <string name="sof_defence"><![CDATA[Globalization and technological advancement have totally changed the perception about the security of a nation. To cope with time and to meet the growing challenges of security threats both at the national and international fronts; Noida International University offers a unique training faculty called the ‘School of Defence, Security &amp; Intelligence’. The faculty offers an extensive range of Diploma &amp; Certified Courses for Graduates, Undergraduates and Ex-Servicemen for durations varying from 2 months to 12 months. Courses are specifically customized to provide solutions to Indian as well as International markets standard. Training is conducted by professional trainers (Ex Army, NSG, SPG             &amp; ITBP Black CAT Commandos).  Candidates have the option of selecting one or all of these programmes for their personal benefit or for their career advancement.]]></string>

</resources>
